<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Iman Bytes</string>

    <string name="topic_all">All</string>

    <string name="title_quran">Quran</string>
    <string name="desc_quran">Discover the miracles of Quran and get to know it.</string>

    <string name="title_seerah">Seerah</string>
    <string name="desc_seerah">Biography of our beloved prophet Muhammad (S.A.W).</string>

    <string name="title_dua">Dua</string>
    <string name="desc_dua">Learn duas that were recited by the prophets.</string>

    <string name="title_hadith">Hadith</string>
    <string name="desc_hadith">An unique way to learn Hadith.</string>

    <string name="title_pillars">Pillars</string>
    <string name="desc_pillars">An unique way to learn the pillars of islam.</string>

    <string name="test_verse_title">Allah Places Inspiration in us in Many Ways</string>
    <string name="test_verse">رَفِيعُ ٱلدَّرَجَـٰتِ ذُو ٱلْعَرْشِ يُلْقِى ٱلرُّوحَ مِنْ أَمْرِهِۦ عَلَىٰ مَن يَشَآءُ مِنْ عِبَادِهِۦ لِيُنذِرَ يَوْمَ ٱلتَّلَاقِ</string>
    <string name="test_verse_translation">[He is] the Exalted above [all] degrees, Owner of the Throne; He places the inspiration of His command [i.e., revelation] upon whom He wills of His servants to warn of the Day of Meeting.</string>
    <string name="test_verse_info">- Surah %s, Verse %s</string>
    <string name="test_verse_tafsir">The root of many deviations is, in fact, the underestimation of God. Man is lost in admiration of other kinds of greatness, because he is unaware of God’s unlimited Greatness. He considers attachment to great men the means of his salvation. When Doomsday removes the veils over people’s eyes, they will come to know that God was and still is so great that the world could be enclosed in His fist like a small coin and the sky could be wrapped around His hand like an ordinary piece of paper.

Just as a bell rings as soon as an examination is over, similarly as soon as the time of the world is over, a trumpet will be blown. After that, the whole system will change. Thereafter, a new world will come into existence.

This present world of ours is illuminated by the light of the sun, which is able to show us only tangible things. The world of the Hereafter will be directly illuminated by God’s light (nur). So even the intangible realities of the world will become visible to man’s eyes. At that time, people will be brought in to the Court of God. In the present world, people ignored the prophets and the preachers operating under their guidance. But, in the Hereafter, people will be wonderstruck to find that their future is decided on the basis of the support or rejection of these prophets and preachers.</string>

    <string name="title_arabic_recitation">Arabic Recitation</string>
    <string name="desc_arabic_recitation">Arabic Recitation of the Quran.</string>
    <string name="arabic_recitation_spl">Best for Memorization</string>

    <string name="title_translation_recitation">Recitation with Translation</string>
    <string name="desc_translation_recitation">Arabic Recitation of the Quran with Realtime Translation.</string>
    <string name="translation_recitation_spl">Best for Understanding</string>
    <string name="recitation_description">“(it is) a Book (the Quran) which We have sent down to you, full of blessings, that they may ponder over its Verses, and that men of understanding may remember.” [Sad 38:29],
</string>

</resources>